memotoo.com 2019-07-11

# Memotoo: Privacy Policy

[**Memotoo.com**](https://www.memotoo.com/) will store your personal data with great care because 

_**your data are your property**_

.  
This Privacy Policy is part of the **Memotoo Terms of Use**.  
By using this site, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and respect it.

**

## 1 - _INFORMATION COLLECTED_

**

  * **The information you provide** We collect and process the information you voluntarily provide in order to use our services (such as your e-mail, your contacts, your calendar, ...) and the data to better understand your preferences to use our service.  
Opening an account and the provision of personal data are not required to use our service. Some personal data may be required to access certain features of our service (such as your address to determine the route to go to one of your contact).  
In no case, we do not collect or handle personal data revealing, directly or indirectly, your racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, philosophical or religious, your union membership, health or sexual orientation.

  * **Cookies**   
When you access to [**Memotoo**](https://www.memotoo.com/) pages, we can send one or more cookies (small files containing a string of characters) to your computer to store data in your browser. They are used to improve the functioning of our service.

  * **Login Information**   
When you connect to [**Memotoo**](https://www.memotoo.com/), it may be that we store your connection information such as your browser, IP address, ...

  * **Communications with other people**   
When you send an e-mail, SMS, ... we do not store the content of these messages.

**

## 2 - _PRIVACY OF YOUR DATA_

**

**[**Memotoo**](https://www.memotoo.com/) will NEVER distribute your information to third persons whether for commercial purposes or not (eg: sell the e-mail addresses, ...).**

**Your personal information are your property and[ **Memotoo**](https://www.memotoo.com/) is only a means to use them with innovative and useful features.**

**

## 3 - _SECURITY OF YOUR DATA_

**

To access the site, you connect with a login and password. It is necessary to choose a password that is not readily available to avoid any risk of piracy. To not steal your login, it is important to know which place you enter and it is strongly recommended to use SSL connections to encrypt data exchanged during the connection [**Memotoo**](https://www.memotoo.com/).  
[ **Memotoo**](https://www.memotoo.com/) sets up ways for the attackers can not access your data, and encryption of your data.  
Your data are only accessible by you, the people you have shared your information, and [**Memotoo**](https://www.memotoo.com/) team.

**

## 4 - _UPDATE YOUR DATA_

**

At any time you can edit and delete all of your personal data via the interfaces of the site.  
You have a right to access, modify, rectify and delete your personal data.

**

## 5 - _AMENDMENT OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY_

**

This Privacy Policy is subject to change and be updated at any time without notice.  
You are therefore advised to regularly check the latest version always available on the site.
